Guide to the Clark, Hall, and Peck and White Brothers Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- White Brothers, 1880s-1982; Series I
  - Other Connecticut cities and towns
    - East Haven
      - Abstracts of title
        - Massachusetts Avenue, Maturo Drive, Maynard Road, McLay Avenue, Meadow Street, Meadow Place, Meriline Avenue, Methuen Avenue, Miami Street, Michael Avenue, Mill Street, Miller Street, Minors Road (Box 566)
        - Main Street (North side, odd number street addresses 57 through 673-683, non-street number files) (Box 567)
        - Main Street (South side, even number street addresses 16 through 686, non-street number files) (Box 568)
        - McKinley Avenue, Momauguin Avenue, "Momauguin Heights" (Cosey Beach Avenue), Montauk Road, Morgan Avenue, Morgan Terrace, Morris Road, Morton Court, Moulthrop Street, Mountain Road, Mountain View Terrace, Myrtle Avenue, Naugatuck Avenue, Naugatuck Street, Navarro Road, Newton Street (Box 569)
        - Nicholas Drive, North Street, North Branford Road, Northeast Drive, Oakhill Drive, "Oak Terrace" (Burr Street), O'Donnell Court, Old Stone Lane, Old Town Hwy., Ora Avenue, Orchard Road, Oregon Avenue, Osmond Street, Ozone Road, "Palisades" (Short Beach Road), Palmetto Trail, Pardee Place, Pardee Place Ext., Pardee Street, "Pardee Plot" (Main Street), Park Place, Park Street, Paul Avenue, Paul Street (Box 570)
        - Pennsylvania Avenue, Pequot Street, Pershing Street, Phillip Street, Pine Place, Pine Street, Pine View Drive, Pioneer Drive, Pleasant Avenue, Pond Street, Pratt Avenue, Pevetty Drive, Prospect Lane, Prospect Place, Prospect Place Ext., Prospect Road, Rabbit Rock Road, Ray Street, Raymond Court, Raynham Street, Raynham Road, Richard Way, Richmond Street, Ridge Street, River Road, River Street, Riverside Annex, Riverside Terrace, "Riverside Terrace" (Box 571)
        - Rizzo Street, Robert Drive, Robin Drive, Rock Road, Rock Street, Rock Terrace, Rock View Road, Rockland Avenue, Roma Street, Rose Street, Rowe Court, Rowe Street, Roy Street, Russo Avenue, Street Andrew Street, Street Paul Avenue, Street Vincent Avenue (Box 572)
        - Salerno Avenue, "Saltonstall Manor," Saltonstall Pkwy, Saltonstall Place, Sanford Street, Savoy Street, Seaview Avenue, Second Avenue, Seneca Trail, "Sheldon Park" (Silver Sands Road), Shell Beach, Shepherd's Grove, Short Road (Box 573)
        - Short Beach Road, Sibley Lane, Sidney Street, Smith Avenue, Sorrento Avenue, Sound View Avenue (Box 574)
          For "Smith Manor", see Cosey Beach Avenue.
        - "Silver Lawn Park" (Dodge Avenue), Silver Sands Road, "Smith Manor" (Cosey Beach Avenue) (Box 575)
        - South Dale Street, South Street, Spencer Street, Sperry Lane, Sperry Road, Spring Road, Stevens Street, Stoddard Road, Street's Point Road, Strong Street, South Strong Street, Summit Avenue (Box 576)
        - Sunset Pass, Sunset Road, Sutton Street, Taft Street, "Talmadge Hill", Talmadge Avenue, Talmadge Street, South End, South End Road, Taylor Avenue, "Thompson Gardens,"Thompson Street (Box 577)
        - Taugoda Pass, Tegner Street, "Thompson Avenue Gardens" (Thompson Avenue), Thornton Drive, Treadwell Street, "Tuttle Grove" (Iver Avenue), "Tuttle Place" (High Street), Tuttle Place, Twiss Street, Union Avenue, Ure Avenue, Van Horn Drive, Vass Street, Venice Place, Vera Street, Vernon Street, Victor Street (Box 578)
        - Thomas Court, Thompson Avenue (Box 579)
        - Tyler Street, View Street, View Terrace, Viking Street (Box 580)
        - Vincent Place, Virginia Road, Vista Drive, Waldo Street, Walter Street, Warner Avenue, Warner Road, Warwick Lane, Washington Avenue, "Washington Park" (Dodge Avenue), Weber Street, "Wellington Park" (Ure Avenue), West Street, West Bretton Street, Wheaton Road, Wheelbarrow Lane, Whitman Avenue (Box 581)
        - Wildwood Drive, Wilkenda Avenue, William Street, Williams Road, Willow Road, Wilson Street, Winchester Place, Windsor Street, Woodland Avenue, Zolan Drive, East Haven Miscellaneous Files (Box 582)
      - Flat Files
        - Anderson Gym Co. (Box 583)
        - Branford Manor (Box 583)
        - Burr Street Terrace (Box 583)
        - Coe Estates (Box 583)
        - East Haven Cut Off (Box 583)
        - East Lawn Cemetery (Box 583)
        - "Elvira Park" (Box 583)
        - Englewood Grove (Box 583)
        - Fairlawn Terrace (Box 583)
        - Fairview Terrace (Box 583)
        - First and Second Sts., (proposed map) (Box 584)
        - "Foxon Park" (Box 584)
        - "Glenmoor" (Box 584)
        - Haven Estates (Box 584)
        - 16 Hemingway Avenue (Box 584)
        - High Ridge (Sections A-B-C-D-E-F-G) (Box 584)
        - "Homewood Heights" (Box 584)
        - Howe Farm (Box 584)
        - Jewish Cemetery (Box 584)
        - Julius Drive (Box 585)
        - Laurel Street (Box 585)
        - Main Street (Box 585)
        - Mansfield Park (Box 585)
        - Maplevale (Box 585)
        - Medallion Grove (Box 585)
        - 1000 Morgan Avenue (Box 585)
        - Oak Nut Park & Annex (Box 585)
        - Panorama Valley (Box 585)
        - Phi Foxon Condominiums (Box 585)
        - Pineview Acres (Box 585)
        - Riverdale (Box 585)
        - "Riverside" (Box 585)
        - Riverside (Box 586)
        - Riverside Terrace (Box 586)
        - Saltonstall Manor (Box 586)
        - Saltonstall Terrace (Box 586)
        - Street Vincent Gardens (Box 586)
        - Silver Sands Estates (Box 586)
        - Summit Gardens (Box 586)
        - Valley Spring (Box 586)
        - Warner, Herbert E. (Box 586)
        - "Woodview" (Box 586)
        - Zolan Estates (Box 586)
    - East Lyme
      - Abstract of title (Box 587)
      - Flat file (Box 587)
    - Easton abstract of title (Box 587)
    - Essex
      - Abstracts of title (Box 587)
      - Flat file (Box 587)
    - Fairfield
      - Abstracts of title (Box 587)
      - Flat file (Box 587)
    - Goshan abstract of title (Box 587)
    - Guilford
      - Index card locator file (Box 588)
      - Abstracts of title
        - 1-70 (Box 589)
        - 71-140 (Box 590)
        - 141-210 (Box 591)
        - 211-280 (Box 592)
        - 281-350 (Box 593)
        - 351-420 (Box 594)
        - 421-520 (Box 595)
        - 521-621, Guilford miscellaneous records (Box 596)
      - Flat files
        - 1-2-3, 9-10, 20, 24, 21-22-23 (Box 597)
        - 83, 90, 91, 111, 128, 130, 139, 144, 148, 158 (Box 598)
        - 178, 179, 206, 207, 219, 221, 222, 229 (Box 599)
        - 239, 290, 307, 308, 334, 336, 339, 363, 374, 381 (Box 600)
        - 388, 392, 407, 410-412, 423, 439, 440, 446, 452, 456, 470, 498, 501, 553, 558 (Box 601)
      - Unnumbered flat files
        - John Beattie estate, 3 (Box 602)
        - "Beattie - Grantor", 2 (Box 602)
        - "Clark" (Guilford) (Box 602)
        - "Gould Home, Madison-Guilford" (Box 602)
        - "Hall" (Box 602)
          The material pertains to different properties in Guilford.
        - "Portions of Master Survey" (Box 602)
          The material pertains to the Old Quarry in Guilford.
    - Haddam
      - Abstract of title (Box 603)
      - Flat file (Box 603)
    - Hamden
      - Abstracts of title
        - Abby Lane, Academy Hill, Adams Street, Addison Road, Albert Road, "Alenier, H. J. map of,"Alenier Street, Allene Drive, Alling Street, Alstrum Street, Amherst Street, Amos Street, Ann's Farm Road, Andover Road, Andrew Street, Apple Tree Lane, Arcadia Street (Box 604)
        - Arch Street, Ardmore Street, Armory Street, Armstrong Street, Athol Place, Atlas Street (Box 605)
        - Augur Street, Austen Road (Box 606)
        - Bagley Avenue, Baker Road, Baldwin Road, Bank Street, Barbara Lane, Baron Road, Barraclough Avenue, Barrett Street, Battis Road, Beacon Street, Bear Path, Beaver Street (Box 607)
        - "Beecher Heights Development," "Belvidere Development,""Benham Heights Development,"Bedford Avenue, Beechwood Avenue, Belden Road, Belmont Street, Benham Street, Bender Road (Box 608)
        - Birchwood Drive, Benton Street, Berkeley Court, Bismark Court (Dixwell Avenue Park), Bittersweet Lane, Blacy Street (Highland Terrace), Blake Road, Bliss Avenue, Blue Hills Avenue (Park Acres), Bolton Street, Bonnie View Drive, Bowen Street, Branford Road (Box 609)
        - Bradley Avenue, Braeside Drive, Brenton Terrace, Brentwood, Brentwood Drive, Brentwood Terrace, Briar Lane, Briarcliff Road, Brinsmade Road, Broadfield Road, Broadway, "Broadway Manor" (Box 610)
        - Brook Street, Brookhaven Road, Brook Hill Road, "Brookside" (West Helen Street), Brookside Drive, Brooksvale Avenue, Brown Street, Bryden Terrace, Building Brook Road, Burke Street, Butler Street, Calamus Meadow Road (Dunbar Hill Road), Cannon Street (Sunnyside Heights), Cardo Road (Box 611)
        - Carew Road, Carleton Street, Carmalt Street, Carmel Street (Norwood), Caroline Street, Carrington Court (Dixwell Terrace), Carrington Street (Dixwell Terrace), Carroll Road, Cassella Drive, "Cedars" (Whitney Avenue), Central Avenue, Chandler Place, Charlson Lane, Chatterton Way, Chauncey Road (Box 612)
        - Cherry Ann Street, Cherry Hill Road, Chester Street, Chestnut Lane, Choate Avenue, Church Street, Churchill Road (Box 613)
        - Circular Avenue, "Colonial Manor" (Waite Street) (Box 614)
        - Claire Terrace ("Park Acres"), Clark Street, Clifford Street, Clover Circle, Cole Road, Collier Circle, Collins Street, Colonial Drive, Colony Street, Concord Street, Connolly Parkway (Box 615)
        - Connell Street, Cook Street, Cooper Lane, Coram Street, Corbin Road, Cornell Street (Arch Street), "Country Club Gardens" (Putnam Avenue), "Country Club Gardens Annex" (Augur Street), Country Club Manor (Hartford Turnpike), "Countryside" (Ridge Road), Country Hills Road, Cross Street, Cumley Street, Cumpstone Drive, Curry Road, Dadio Road, Dallas Street (Box 616)
        - Daniel Road, Dante Place, Darley Drive, Davis Street, Dawes Avenue, Dawes Street, Day Spring Avenue, Dean Avenue, Deepwood Drive, Deerfield Drive, Delsole Road (Box 617)
        - Denslow Hill Road, Depot Avenue, Dessa Avenue, Dest Drive, Dest Road, Dickerman Street, Dix Street, Doren Avenue, Dorrance Place, Dorrance Street, Downs Road, Duane Road, Dudley Street (Box 618)
        - Dixwell Avenue (Even number street addresses 1416 through 2998-3000) (Box 619)
        - Dixwell Avenue (Even number street addresses 800 through 1300) (Box 620)
        - Dixwell Avenue (Odd number street addresses 809 through 1827) (Box 621)
        - Dixwell Avenue (Odd number street addresses 1883 through 3039-3055, non-street number files) (Box 622)
        - Dixwell Avenue Developments: "Beecher Heights," "Benham Heights," "Dixwell Avenue Park," "Dixwell Manor," "Dixwell Terrace," "Grand View Heights," "Hamden Park," "Lake View Crest," "Lake View Crest Ext.," "Lenox Place," "Notkins Lots," "Prospect Park," "Clark R. Shelton Lots," "Shepard Avenue Dev.," "VonBeren & Nicklas," "Wolcott and Holt" (Box 623)
        - Dunbar Hill Road, Dunn Road, Earl Avenue, East Clover Road, Eastland Road, Easton Street, Eber Street, Edgecomb Street, Edgehill Road, Edgehill Terrace, Edgemere Road, East Gate Lane (Box 624)
        - Edgewood Avenue, Edwards Street, Eleanor Street, Elgin Street, Elihu Street, Elizabeth Road, Elliot Drive, Elm Street, Elmer Avenue, Elmwood Place, Eramo Terrace (Box 625)
        - Evergreen Avenue, Exeter Road, "Fairlawn Park," Fairview Avenue, "Fair View Manor" (Harmon Street), "Fair View Terrace" (Whitney Avenue), Fallon Drive (Box 626)
        - Fans Rock Road, Farmington Drive, Farnsworth Street, Farrell Street, "Fawn Ridge," Federal Street, Fennbrook Drive, Fenway Drive, Fenwick Street, Fern Street, Fernwood Street, Field Crest Lane, Filbert Street, First Street, Fitch Street, Flight Road, Flower Drive (Box 627)
        - "Florence Terrace" (Church Street), Foch Street, Foote Street, Ford Street, Forest Court South, Forest Street, Four Rod Road, Fourth Street, Fowler Street, Francis Avenue, Franklin Road, Frazier Road, Friend Street, Funaro Road, Furman Lane, Furman Road (Box 628)
        - "Galawn" (Washington Avenue), Gale Place, Garden Street, Garfield Street, Garvin Road, Gaylord Mountain Road, George Street, Gessner Place, Gilbert Avenue, Giles Street, Gillies Road, Glemby Street (Box 629)
        - Glen Parkway, Glenbrook Avenue, Glendale Street, Glendower Road, Glenham Road, Goebel Road, "Goodrich Farm" (Newhall Street), Goodrich Street, Goodsell Road, Gordon Street (Box 630)
        - Gorham Avenue, Gorham Drive, Grafton Road, Grandview Avenue (Box 631)
        - "Grand View Heights" (Dixwell Avenue), "Grand View Ridge," Green Hill Road, Greenway Street, Haig Street, Hall Street, "Hamden Park" (Dixwell Avenue), "Hamden Plains Co." (Circular Avenue), Hampshire Drive, Hampton Road, Handy Road, Harding Street, Harmon Street, Harris Street, Harrison Drive, Haverford Street (Box 632)
        - Hartford Tpke., Hawley Road, Hawthorne Avenue, Hayward Road, Haywood Lane (Box 633)
        - Hearn Lane, Heather Road, Heathridge Road, Helen Street, Heloise Street, Hepburn Road, Hesse Road, High Lane, Highland Avenue (Box 634)
        - "Highland Terrace" (Pine Rock Avenue), Highmeadow Road, High Ridge Road, High Rock Road, High Top Circle, Highwood Avenue, Hill Street, High Street (Box 635)
        - Hillcrest Avenue, Hillfield Road, Hill Top Rd (Four Rod Hwy.), Hillview Avenue, Hobson Avenue, Hodder Drive, Hodder Road, Hogan Road, Home Place, "Homelands," Homelands Terrace, Home Place, Homestead Avenue, Hope Avenue, Howard Avenue, Howard Drive, Howell Avenue, "Hubbard Farm" (State Street), Hubbard Place, Hubbard Road, Hubbard Street, Hudson Street, Humiston Avenue, Huntington Circle, Ingleside Drive, Ingram Street, Ives Street (Box 636)
        - Jackson Road, Jaenicke Lane, James Street, Jamestown Road, Jayne Lane, Jean Street, Jennifer Road, Jesswig Drive, Johnson Road, Jo-Mar Drive, Jones Road, Joyce Road, Julian Drive, Katherine Street, Katherine Drive, Kelly Road, "Kenwood," Kenwood Avenue, "Kerrigan" (Putnam Avenue) (Box 637)
        - Killdeer Road, Kimberly Avenue, King Street, Kirk Road, Klarman Drive, Knob Hill Drive, Knoll Drive, Koury Terrace, Laconia Street, Lake Street, "Lakeside Manor" (Waite Street), Lakeview Avenue, Lake View Crest, Lake View Crest Ext., Lakewood Manor" (Mather Street), Lamkin Street, Lane Street, Lansdowne Avenue, Larkspur Lane, Laura Road (Box 638)
        - Laurel Street, Lawrence Road, Leeds Street, "Lenox Place" (Dixwell Avenue), Leo Road, Leonard Road, Lexington Street, Lilac Avenue, Lillibridge Court, Lincoln Street, "Lincoln Terrace" (Gorham Avenue), Linden Avenue, Lloyd Street, Locust Street, Loller Road, London Drive (Box 639)
        - Longmeadow Avenue, Lovig Lane, Lucien Drive, Lucy Street, Luzerne Avenue, Lynmoor Place, Lynmot Road, MacArthur Drive, Magee Drive, Maher Avenue, Main Street, Malcom Street, Manila Avenue, Manor Street, Manspur Road, Maple Street, "Maple Lawn" (Circular Avenue), Maplewood Terrace, Marietta Street, Marion Avenue (Box 640)
        - Marlboro Street, Marne Street, Marshall Road, Martin Terrace, Mather Street, McDermott Circle, Meadow Brook Road, "Meadow Brook Country Club", Megin Drive, Melrose Avenue (Box 641)
        - Merrimac Street, Merritt Street, Michael Road, Middle Road, Middlevale Road, Mill Rock Road, Millis Street, Mix Avenue, Monroe Street, Morgan Lane, Morris Street, Midwood Court, Midhill Drive (Box 642)
        - Morse Street, Mott Street, Moulton Street, Mountain View Terrace (Box 643)
          For Mountain Road, see Main Street.
        - Mount Carmel Avenue, Mount Sanford Street, Newhall Street, Mueller Drive, Mulberry Hill Street, Murlyn Street (Box 644)
        - Murray Street, Nesbit Road, New Road, Newbury Street, Newcastle Drive, Newton Street, Nista Drive, Noble Court, Norman Road, Norris Street, North Street, North Lake Drive (Box 645)
        - North Sheffield Street, Norton Avenue, "Norwood" (Whitney Avenue), Norwood Avenue, Notkins Street, Oberlin Street, October Hill Road, Old Coach Hwy., Old Hill Road, Olympia Avenue, Orchard Court, Orchard Street, Orchard Heights Drive, Oregon Avenue, Orient Lane, Orpington Street, Pacific Street, Palmer Avenue, Paradise Avenue (Box 646)
        - Paramount Avenue, "Park Acres," Park Avenue, Park Road (Parkside Road), Park View Road, Parmelee Drive, Patterson Road, Patterson Hill Road, Pearl Avenue, Pearl Park, Pease Road, Peck Lane, Pelham Avenue, Pembroke Road, Penn Street, Perrone Road, Perry Road, Pershing Street (Box 647)
          For "Park View Heights", see Newcastle Drive.
        - Phelps Drive, Pickwick Road, Pine Street, "Pine Brook Gardens," Pine Rock (Fowler Street), Pine Rock Avenue, "Pine Rock Terrace" (Arch Street), Pinewood Road, Piper Road, Plains Avenue, Pleasant Drive (Box 648)
        - Pond Road, "Park Acres," Prospect Court, "Homelands," Prospect Lane, "Homelands," "Prospect Park" (Dixwell Avenue), Prospect Street, Prospect Terrace, "Homelands," Putnam Avenue, Promenade Drive. (Box 649)
        - Quaker Road, Quentin Street, Raelin Road, Ralston Avenue, Ranch Road, "Raymond Gardens" (Rochford Avenue), Read, T.R (Morse Street), Red Rock Terrace, Remington Street, Renshaw Road, Rentell Road, Reyna Road, (Pine Brook Gardens), Richard Drive, "Ridge Top Farms" (Ridge Road), Ridgewood Avenue, River Road, River Street, Riverside Drive, Robert Street, Robinwood Road (Box 650)
        - Ridge Road, "Ridge Road Village" (Box 651)
        - Rochford Avenue, Rockview Road, Rockwood Avenue, Rockwood Road, Rocky Top Road, Rogers Road, Rolfe Road, Rolling Ridge Road, Roosevelt Street, Rose Street, Rosedale Road, "Rosehurst Acres" (S. Benham Street), Rowe &Converse(Mather Street), Rosemary Lane, Rosina Road, Russell Street, Russo Drive, Russo Road (Box 652)
        - Saint Ann Street, Saint James Street, Saint Mary Street, Street Mihiel Drive, Sandquist Circle, Sanford Street, Santa Fe Avenue, Savoy Street, School Street, Schupp Road, Scott Street, Sebec Street, Second Street, Seminole Avenue, Sheahan, Drive, Shelton Avenue, Shelton, Clark R. (Map of Gorham Avenue) (Box 653)
        - Shepard Avenue, Shepard Street (Box 654)
        - Sherman Lane, Sherman Avenue, Sidehill Road, Skiff Street, Sleeping Giant Drive, Sleeping Giant Manor, Smith Drive, Sunwoods Circle, South New Road, Springdale Street (Box 655)
        - Spring Garden Street, "Spring Glen Estates," Spring Glen Terrace, Spruce Bank Road, Stanley Road, "Steinert Estates," Sterling Place, Stevens Street, Stillhill Road, Stonewall Drive, Summit Street, "Sunnyside Heights" (Cannon Street), Sunset Road, Swathmore Street, "Sylvan Homes" (Box 656)
        - State Street (Street addresses 1655-1673 through 2466) (Box 657)
        - State Street (Street addresses 2520 through 2980, non-street number files) (Box 658)
        - Tanglewood Drive, Taft Street, "Tenacre" (Whitney Avenue), Terrace Avenue, Thayer Street, Third Street, Thomas Street, Thorpe Drive, Thurl Avenue, Tierney Road, Todd Street, Tom Swamp Road, Treadwell Street (Box 659)
        - Talmadge Knoll, Thompson Street, Thorton Street, Towne House Road (Box 660)
        - Troiano Road, Turnor Avenue, Tuttle Avenue, Twinbrook Road, Underhill Road, Ursini Drive, Valley Road (Box 661)
        - "Vantage Ground," Vantage Road, Veranda Avenue, Vernon Street, Victor Street, Villa Road, Vincent Street, Vineyard Road, Violet Street, Wadsworth Street, Wagner Drive (Box 662)
        - Waite Street, Wakefield Street, Walden Street, Walter Lane, Warner Street, Warren Street (Box 663)
        - Washngton Avenue, Washington Court, Washington Road, Watson Street, Wayne Street, Webb Street, "Weiss Park (Wooding Street), Welch Street (Box 664)
        - Welton Street, Wescott Road, West Easton Street, Westerfield Road, West Helen Street ("Pine Brook Gardens"), "Westerleigh," West Meadow Road (Box 665)
        - Westminster Street, West Prospect Street, West Shepard Street, West Side Drive, West Slope Lane, West Todd Avenue (Box 666)
        - Westview Street, West Woods Road, Weybossett Avenue, Wheeler Street, Wood Street (Box 667)
        - Woodine Street, White Drive, "Whiting Park," Whiting Street, Whitney Court, "Whitneyville Terrace" (Waite Street), Wilbert Street, Wilkins Street, Willard Street, Williamson Road, Willow Street, Willowcrest Drive, "Wilmot," Wilmot Road, Wilson Lane, Wilton Road, Windsor Road, Winett Street, Wiscassett Street (Box 668)
        - Whitney Avenue (West side, even number street addresses 1030 through 2598) (Box 669)
        - Whitney Avenue (West side, even number street addresses 2600 through 4510) (Box 670)
        - Whitney Avenue (East side, odd number street addresses 841-845 through 2699) (Box 671)
        - Whitney Avenue (East side, odd number street addresses 2701 through 4399) (Box 672)
        - Whitney Avenue (Non-street number files) (Box 673)
        - Whitney Avenue Developments: "The Cedars," "Fair View Terrace," "Linsky Property," "Norwood," "Joseph Pavis Lots," "John H. Rochford Lots," "Spring Glen Estates," "Spring Glen Heights," "Spring Glen Manor," "Spring Glen Ridge," "Tenacre," "Whitney Park," "Whitney Terrace" (Box 674)
        - Winchester Avenue, Wintergreen Avenue (Box 675)
        - Wooding Street (Box 676)
        - Woodland Avenue, Woodlawn Street, Woodruff Street, Woodstock Road and Hamden miscellaneous records (Box 677)
        - Hamden miscellaneous records (Box 678)
      - Flat files
        - "Academy Hill" (Box 679)
        - Admiral Realty Co., Inc. (Box 679)
        - Alenier, Henry J. (63 building lots) (Box 679)
        - Apple Orchard Homesites (Box 679)
        - Augar Estates (Box 679)
        - Barnett Development Corp. (Box 679)
        - Bear Path Development Co. (Box 679)
        - Beecher Heights (Box 679)
        - Bella Vista Terrace (Box 679)
        - Belvidere (Box 679)
        - Benham Lane Heights (Box 679)
        - "Benson Acres" (Box 679)
        - Blue Hills (Box 680)
        - Blue Hills Development (Box 680)
        - Bonnie View Acres (Box 680)
        - "Braeside" (Box 680)
        - Brentwood (Box 680)
        - Brewster, William (Box 680)
        - Broadview Manor (Box 680)
        - Brookvale (Box 680)
        - Butterorth, Frank (Mt. Carmel, Tuttle Avenue) (Box 680)
        - Charlton Hill Condominium (Box 680)
        - Circular Avenue Tract 2 (Box 680)
        - "Colonial Farms" (Box 680)
        - Connecticut Brick (Box 681)
        - "Cooper Hill" (Box 681)
        - Country Hills (Box 681)
        - Dickerman Development (Box 681)
        - Dickerman, Elihu and Elizabeth S. Barnes (Box 681)
        - Dickerman, Wales C. (Box 681)
        - 2175 to 2187 Dixwell Avenue (Fairmont Foods Company) (Box 681)
        - Dixwell Manor (Box 681)
        - Dolittle, James, Arthur M, and Ruth J. (Box 681)
        - "Edgewood" (Box 681)
        - Elliot Hill (Box 681)
        - Evergreen Acres (Sections 1-2) (Box 681)
        - Evergreen Avenue (8 acres) (Box 681)
        - Fairlawn Park (Box 682)
        - Fairview Farms (Box 682)
        - Farm Hill Development & Condominiums (Box 682)
        - Field Crest Manor (Box 682)
        - Flower Estates (Box 682)
        - Forest Hills (Sections 1, 2, 3) (Box 682)
        - Forest Homes (Box 682)
        - Gaylord Village (Box 682)
        - Gilbert, A.C. (Box 683)
        - Gilbert, Albert C. (Box 683)
        - Gilbert Homes (Box 683)
        - Gilles, James A. (Box 683)
        - Gioriano Construction Co. (Box 683)
        - Grand View Ridge (Box 683)
        - Harris, B. Malcolm (Box 683)
        - 106-109 Hartford Turnpike (Box 683)
        - Henry Homes Inc. (Box 683)
        - Hepburn Ridge (Box 683)
        - Hepburn Ridge Condominiums (Box 683)
        - "Homeland" (Box 683)
        - Kenwood (Box 684)
        - Knob Hill (Box 684)
        - Knollwood Acres (Box 684)